Contact

rafiun94@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/md-rafi-un-noor-washik-811787107 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

User Interface Design
Miro Collaboration Platform
Zeplin

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Bengali (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Limited Working)
Dutch (Elementary)

Certifications

Designing a Low Fidelity Prototype in Figma

Urban Nature: Connecting Cities, Sustainability and Innovation

Associate Member

Greening the Economy: Sustainable Cities

ACCENTURE Certified DIGITAL SKILLS: USER EXPERIENCE

Md. Rafi Un Noor Washik

Architect | Interior Designer | UX Designer | Associate Architect at Studio SpaceJam | UX Designer at Bayanno Vuj | Dhaka, Bangladesh

Summary

I am an architect and interior designer. I have been working in this sector for almost 5 years. I have good skills with software like: Sketch up, AutoCAD, Revit, Lumion, Adobe creative suite etc.. I have a good experience on site works too as I had to do it for both my workplace.

I've been trying to learn and working as an User Experience
Designer . I've done courses and workshops to understand and
imply UX and UI design. After that I joined Bayanno Vuj as an intern
UX designer. I learned the marketing side and practical aspects of
UX design and gained promotion in there as an UX designer . I'm still
learning UX designed in my everyday professional life.

I have expertise in Figma, Fig jam, Miro, Zeplin, Sketch etc. I'm learning adobe XD too but still I feel comfortable in working figma.

Experience

Studio SpaceJam Associate Architect November 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months) Dhaka, Bangladesh

Bayanno Vuj UX Designer April 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months) Dhaka, Bangladesh

LIVING HOME DEVELOPMENTS LIMITED Head Of Design Department September 2020 - November 2021 (1 year 3 months) Dhaka, Bangladesh IshaTech Advertising Ltd Junior Architect January 2019 - July 2020 (1 year 7 months) Dhaka

Worked here to serve as an architect and interior designer.

Enbreathe Architects
Architectural Intern
July 2018 - December 2018 (6 months)
Malibag , Dhaka

Education

Stamford University Bangladesh
Bachelor of Architecture - BArch, Architecture and Related Services · (April 2013 - July 2018)